{"data":[{"question":"That kind madam told me how he had given me shelter and protection without which I ___ of hunger.","a":"would have died","b":"would be died","c":"will die","d":"would die","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Were it not for the debts, our family ___ all right.","a":"would have been","b":"would be","c":"are","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Had I known her name, ___.","a":"she will come here","b":"I will invite her to lunch or dinner","c":"I would have invited her to lunch or dinner","d":"she would come here","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle \n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"I realize that you were driving at 120 mph, don't you? \"No, officer, I ___. This kind of car can't do more than 90.\"","a":"may not have been","b":"cannot be","c":"needn't have been","d":"couldn't have been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You _________ the washing. Aaron would have done it for you.","a":"didn't need to have done","b":"needn't have done","c":"mustn't have done","d":"weren't to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Needn't have PP:  means that it was not necessary for someone to do something that they in fact did","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You ___ the look on Vincent's face when he won the first prize.","a":"can be seen","b":"would have seen","c":"should have seen","d":"must see","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used to say what would have been right or sensible, but was not done ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"With all the assignments finished, I ___ to the concert last night.","a":"ought to go","b":"must go","c":"need to go","d":"should have gone","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used to say what would have been right or sensible, but was not done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Joy couldn't have answered the question if she ___ a few books on English literature.","a":"haven't read","b":"hadn't read","c":"didn't read","d":"wouldn't read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: used to talk about things that didn't happened in the past and the consequence if they had happened \n+ Form: if + Past Perfect, would + have + Past Participle ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor did everything he could so that he ___ save the brave soldier's life.","a":"would","b":"can","c":"might","d":"should","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Might: used as the past tense of 'may' when reporting that someone talked or thought about the possibility of something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"I went to the meeting yesterday because I ___ nothing about the discussion without attending it.","a":"would know","b":"didn't know","c":"would have known","d":"knew","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}